<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>job experience on Amir Orbe</title>
    <link>https://amirOrbe.github.io/categories/job-experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in job experience on Amir Orbe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Amir Orbe Site</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amirOrbe.github.io/categories/job-experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Backend Developer at Bunsan</title>
      <link>https://amirOrbe.github.io/post/backend-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amirOrbe.github.io/post/backend-developer/</guid>
      <description>Role Overview: as a Backend Developer I participated in a big e-commerce company.
The challenges in which I support: Resolving bugs of discount campaigns Adding telemetry for some metrics Migrating API&amp;rsquo;s from REST to GraphQL Implementation of a new type of discount Refactoring code Implementation for download dynamic excel generation files with a lot of information. Interesting challenges: The e-commerce project is really big, so I needed to study a lot of topics that I didn’t know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elixir intern at Bunsan</title>
      <link>https://amirOrbe.github.io/post/elixir-intern/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amirOrbe.github.io/post/elixir-intern/</guid>
      <description>Role Overview: As Fullstack Developer I participed in a system for register the projects, skills, skill level, status, occupation time, level in each skill, areas, vacations and assignments of each employee.
The challenges in which I support: Implementation of a new dynamic call to assign a call to employees once a month for interaction between them. Implementation of a new section in the application to generate dynamic reports by date to obtain a summary of each employee Implementation of a new section to assign the corresponding area to each employee Fixing logic bugs Migrating API&amp;rsquo;s from REST to Graphql Implementing a new tool to identify an employee using the phone camera Interesting challenges: The system was the first in which I contributed, so I needed to study new topics that I didn&amp;rsquo;t know before, for example:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
